Hi, this is PolicyPay Agent: a policy-bound autonomous payment agent built on Sui.
It targets the Agentic Web track because the agent can observe state, plan an action, transact on Sui, and coordinate recurring payments inside boundaries enforced by Move.
Recurring crypto payments are still awkward for teams, DAOs, and small protocol treasuries. PolicyPay separates automation from authority.
The owner connects a Sui wallet, creates an AgentVault, and defines hard limits before signing.
Those limits include max payment amount, rolling-window spend, reserve balance, expiry, and the agent wallet receiving the scoped session capability.
Sui produces three important objects: the shared AgentVault, the owner's OwnerCap, and the agent's AgentSessionCap.
The owner deposits SUI and adds a recurring payment rule with recipient, amount, schedule, nonce, and active state stored onchain.
The agent service observes due rules, previews a plan, risk-checks it, and submits the payment transaction with the agent key.
If the agent tries to exceed policy, pay too early, drain the reserve, or continue after pause or revoke, Move aborts the call.
Every meaningful step leaves Sui evidence: package id, vault objects, transaction digest, object state, and events.